originalsignal.com 2007-12-13

# Original Signal » Privacy Policy

**1\. Privacy Policy Original Signal  
**  
**  
Stillpoint Media Privacy Principles**

  * Your information is your own and you decide who will have access to it.
  * You maintain ownership rights to your information, even if there is a business transition or policy change.
  * You may add, delete, or modify your information at any time.
  * Stillpoint Media will not update or modify your information without your permission.
  * Stillpoint Media will not sell, exchange, or otherwise share your information with third parties, unless required by law or in accordance with your instructions.
  * Stillpoint Media does not send spam, maintain spam mailing lists, or support the activities of spammers.

**Cookies**

In order to improve the services and the site, we use “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be understood by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your computer’s identification token and enables Stillpoint Media to personalise your experience when you on the site. If you reject the cookie, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorisation, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)

**Log Files and Backups**

Like most Internet services, we use log files, both on the client and server side. The data held in log files includes your IP address, browser type, e-mail application, Internet service provider (“ISP”), referring/exit Web pages, computer platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity. Stillpoint Media uses server log data to analyse trends, administer the services and the site, and improve service levels. IP addresses are not tied to any personally identifiable Information.

**Links**

The site contains, and the software may present, links to other sites. Please be aware that Stillpoint Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the site or otherwise link to other sites, to read the privacy policies of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. Stillpoint Media Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the site.

The site also contains links to the Original Signal Blog. The blog provides interactive venues for members and others to learn more about Original Signal, receive support from others, and send us feedback. If you use this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit.

**Government Authority**

You should be aware that, as with all legal contracts, our Privacy Policy could be amended, terminated or modified without the consent of you and/or Stillpoint Media by judicial proceeding, court order, in connection with bankruptcy or other insolvency proceedings, or pursuant to other government action. When reasonable and lawful, we will notify you if this occurs.

**Changes to the Stillpoint Media Privacy Policy**

If we change the Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the site with a link from the site’s homepage, so that you are always aware of our Privacy Policy.

We will use your information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we plan to use your information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via e-mail and/or through a notice on our website and any other appropriate methods and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner.

Whether or not you wish to have your information used in this different manner, you will retain ownership rights to your information and the ability to delete your information at any time.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Stillpoint Media  
Oosterdokskade 5 – 4N  
1011 AD Amsterdam  
The Netherlands

or via [e-mail](http://www.stillpoint-media.nl/email.php?w=5&l=1)
